

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

Jakarta Metropolitan Area Indonesia +6281357202812 stanlyskwok@gmail.com

Links

Personal Website LinkedIn

Skills

MongoDB

JavaScript Solidity **Flutter** React Node.js **Next JS** Express JS **PostgreSQL TypeScript** Hardhat

Profile

Hello, I'm a full-stack Web, Mobile and Web3 Developer. I specialize in using React for Web Development, Flutter & React Native for Mobile development and React & Solidity for Web3 Development. I use Node JS for backend development, and PostgreSQL as the database.

Go to this website to view my portfolio: https://stanly-sukmajaya.vercel.app/

Education

Bachelor of Business (Accountancy), United Institute of Technology, Auckland, New Zealand

FEBRUARY 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2019

Employment History

Full Stack Developer, Metabase, Jakarta

JANUARY 2023 - APRIL 2023

Responsibilities:

- Developing and maintaining scalable and efficient frontend architectures that support the development of high-quality web or mobile applications.
- Collaborating with designers, developers, and stakeholders to develop functional and intuitive user interfaces.
- Writing clean and maintainable code that is scalable, efficient, and adheres to established coding standards.
- Troubleshooting and debugging code to ensure that web applications work smoothly and efficiently.
- Managing and optimizing mobile application build processes, including the use of task runners, bundlers, and preprocessors.
- · Integrating frontend code with backend systems, including APIs and
- Developing and maintaining decentralized applications (dApps) on blockchain platforms.

Flutter Developer, Adira Finance, Jakarta

AUGUST 2021 - DECEMBER 2022

Responsibilities:

- Developing mobile apps and web applications for Adira's internal use.
- Developing and maintaining scalable and efficient frontend architectures that support the development of high-quality mobile applications.
- Collaborating with designers, developers, and stakeholders to develop functional and intuitive user interfaces.
- Writing clean and maintainable code that is scalable, efficient, and adheres to established coding standards.
- Troubleshooting and debugging code to ensure that web or mobile applications work smoothly and efficiently.
- Integrating frontend code with backend systems, including APIs and databases.